35 year old architect proffel wants an
increasing life cover an early return of
premiums he chooses a life cover of one
crore rupees that increases by five
percent every
for the next 20 years to cover the most
crucial years
the age of 55 his life cover would
become two crore rupees as his
responsibilities start decreasing his
life cover becomes one crore rupees
between the age of 56 to 60.
he receives early return of premiums of
an amount of 14 lakhs 87 000 rupees as
his responsibilities are further reduced
his life cover becomes 50 lakh rupees
between the age of 61 to 75 on Survival
at age 75 his policy lapses on his
demise at age 54 his family will get 1
crore 95 lakh rupees
pink one step ahead Lake brawful choose
ICICI Pro eye protect return of Premium
with early return of Premium life stage
cover now